<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lucas Cezimbra</title><link>https://cezimbra.me/en/</link><description>Recent content on Lucas Cezimbra</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:51:46 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cezimbra.me/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Talks</title><link>https://cezimbra.me/en/talks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:51:46 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://cezimbra.me/en/talks/</guid><description>Automating financial control with Python (Portuguese) Link to heading Date: 2022-09-10 Event: Python Sul Python to Automate Financial Control (Portuguese) Link to heading Date: 2019-08-17 Event: PyCaxias Description: In this talk I showed how we can use Python and its tools to automate the extraction of your bank data and create a financial control system that is filled automatically. So you can spend time on the most important thing, which is to analyze your finances instead of spending time filling spreadsheets and/or systems.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://cezimbra.me/en/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:49:12 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://cezimbra.me/en/about/</guid><description>Setup Link to heading Notebook Thinkpad T480 Intel Core i5 16 GB RAM SSD HP S700 250GB Debian Bullseye LG LED 23&amp;quot; Monitor on ELG F80N Stand Webcam Logitech C920s + Ring Light Edifier W800BT Headphone + Boya BY-M1 Microphone Logitech M100 Mouse Baseus 6 in 1 Hub dF Metal Arts Desk and Plaxmetal Brizza Presidente Chair Paper and Pen &amp;ldquo;A Mão de São José&amp;rdquo; by Matheus Bazzo in the background.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://cezimbra.me/en/projects/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 20:08:54 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://cezimbra.me/en/projects/</guid><description>Missas.com.br Website with Catholic mass times. hugo-coder-htmx A minimalist Single-page application blog theme for Hugo using HTMX. Agilize Client to access Agilize (Brazilian accouting company). Banco Inter Client to consume Inter (Brazilian Bank) APIs for legal person accounts. PyItau Scraper to access your Itaú (Brazilian) bank data. Django Template An opinionated Django start project template. Cookiecutter PyPackage My Cookiecutter PyPackage fork. dcache Distributed Cache for Humans. django-ultratenant Ultimate Django app for multi-tenant.</description></item></channel></rss>